Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and

Notice Period: 3 Months

Engineering]

Mayur D. Mehar () Featured

Sr. Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Core Java, Spring MVC, Oracle, JavaScript, J-Query, Jasper Report, Ajax, HP Fortify



Current Designation: Senior Software Developer -Core Java

Current Company: Nelito System Pvt. Ltd.

Current Location: Navi Mumbai

Pref. Location: Nagpur, Pune, Navi Mumbai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Sr. Software Developer, Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Core Java, Spring

MVC, Oracle, JavaScript, J-Query, Jasper Report, Ajax, HP Fortify

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Overall, 4.5 years of experience in development of web applications using JAVA and J2EE.

4.5 years of experience in the system analysis, design, development, implementation and delivery of Web and Enterprise products along with Database designing using Java Technologies.

Hands on experience Spring Boot, Restful Web Services, Hibernate.

Hands on experience in Core Java, Spring MVC, JDBC

Worked on B2B and B2C applications with Enterprise, Banking domain.

Worked on Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF).

Worked on payload 256bit encryption Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) is asymmetric encryption algorithm and RSA

Experienced in Design, Coding and Delivery of projects of different life cycles (Agile, OOAD Object Oriented Analysis/Design/Programming and methodologies).

Worked on scanning and securing the code from security vulnerabilities.

Work Experience

Nelito System Pvt. Ltd. as Senior Software Developer -Core Java Jan 2018 to Till Date

Client SBI State Bank of India

Technologies Core Java, Spring MVC, oracle, JavaScript, J-Query, Jasper Report, Ajax, HP Fortify, WebLogic.

Roles & Responsibilities

Involved in Design, Coding, Bug Fixing goes as a combined regular process.

Design and develop Contribution and corporate contribution Module.

Develop Server-side validation Encryption and Decryption.

Participating in architecture design.

R and D of new features that can be integrated with the existing solution.

Working closely with onsite co-coordinator for requirements understanding and interaction with client.

Description

The NPS-Lite is basically designed with the intention to secure the future of the people who are economically disadvantaged and who are not financially well to do. Towards this endeavor NSDL has developed a NPS Lite system on a low charge structure. The servicing model is of NPS Lite is based on group servicing. The people forming part of this low-income groups will be represented through their organizations known as "Aggregators" who would facilitate in subscriber registration, transfer of pension contributions and subscriber maintenance functions. Subscribers in the age group of 18 to 60 can join NPS - Lite through the aggregator and contribute till the age of 60.

MasterSoft Pvt Ltd, as Jr. Software Developer

May 2016 to Jan 2018

Client MasterSoft Pvt Ltd, Nagpur

Technologies Spring MVC, Hibernate3., PostGreSQL, JavaScript, J-Query, Jasper Report.

Roles & Responsibilities

Involved in Design, Coding, Bug Fixing goes as a combined regular process.

Description

Is web-based e-Governance software for computerization of all administrative activities of any Educational Institution such as autonomous institutes, deemed universities & professional colleges. It supports various modern technologies such as online payment gateway, SMS, smart cards, biometrics, email alerts etc. RF-CAMPUS is fully integrated multi-user system with 100% protection against unauthorized access. It provides secured, accurate & timely information to users at all levels for better decision making. RF-CAMPUS improves the overall efficiency of various users & hence improves the performance of the organization as a whole. RF-CAMPUS eliminates duplication of work & hence reduces overall cost & enables better utilization of resources.

Eventsys Technology as Jr. Software Developer

Jun 2015 to May 2016

Client Eventsys Technology, Pune.

Technologies Spring MVC, Hibernate3., PostGreSQL, JavaScript, J-Query, Jasper Report.

Roles & Responsibilities

Involved in Design, Coding, Bug Fixing goes as a combined regular process.

Description

GoEzHealth is web portal. it is a secure web application that gives access to register doctors and patients. By using authentication patient can view its own health record, medication history and schedule appointments. Doctors have an EHR system in which they can manage their patient history and appointments. Doctor generates e-prescription using SNOMED diagnosis and Rx norm medicine database. Doctors are connected with each other and share its patient information and diagnosis details in emergency. Doctors can create its profile it is publically visible. Doctors can gives forum reply upload tips and blogs.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Agnihotri College of engineering, Wardha in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
CORE JAVA	
SPRING MVC	
JDBC	
JavaScript, J-Query	
JASPER REPORT	
Ajax, HP Fortify	

1/22/2021 $https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=d914174f7cb38fd8a0347925a128fac35d0c58074f1b0c420210400b5a0\dots\\ for the contraction of the$

Oracle	
WebLogic	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time